[Forging Justice]
[Episode 12]
Mentor.
I just finished reading
Wang Youxi's case.
It's too egregious.
He molested a woman in the street,
in front of her husband
and son.
If we let him get away with this,
he'll never stop.
So fired up, huh?
You've been here for three years,
and this is your first time
as the lead prosecutor.
It's natural to get invested in a case.
But you have to keep reminding yourself:
Be committed,
but don't get personally entangled.
Because we are prosecutors,
not ordinary citizens.
I understand.
-But this case...
-Chen, someone is looking for you.
Just a minute.
Okay, go ahead.
I'll take a look.
Okay.
[Citizen Reception Office,
Binjiang City People's Procuratorate]
Chen,
going out?
Hey buddy!
Need to file a lawsuit?
Need a legal petition written?
Don't yell here.
When did you get here?
I just arrived.
I was on a business trip to Bindong.
I came here especially to see you.
Looking at your outfit,
you look more and more like a profiteer.
Oh, man.
Aren't you going to find me a good seat?
I earned a lot of money,
but didn't save a dime.
I'm like a guy with a rake
pulling in cash,
but right behind me there's
someone scattering it all away.
Who?
Yuan Yifang,
the great lawyer Yuan.
Chivalrous, pure-hearted—
people call him
the "Never-Winning Wealth-Scatterer."
I'm here burning the midnight oil,
bringing in the business,
and he's out there taking on
pro bono cases left and right.
You know what we call that?
A total waste of time.
Our law firm
can barely keep going now,
which is already pretty good.
You don't need to complain to me.
If you don't want to do it,
just don't work for him.
People
shouldn't just care about money.
We need to have some pursuits, right?
See, you still want to do it.
Okay.
It's good to have him keep you in check.
Wait a moment.
After I get off work,
let's go grab some food.
I've already booked a private room.
Let's invite Xia Yingjie
and Yu Gaoyuan
tonight.
Especially Yu Gaoyuan.
There's something
I need to talk to that jerk about.
What did he do this time?
I ran into Zhang Lihui a few days ago.
I heard she is studying
for her master's degree
under Mr. Zhou, isn't she?
She's not doing well.
Very badly.
Chief Judge, you were looking for me?
Xia.
Come, come in.
I'll close the door.
No need.
Come, sit.
Here's the thing.
The division is planning
to transfer you to Mei Fang's team.
Any objections?
Why?
Mei Fang has had a hard life.
Her husband just passed away
from an illness.
She's only been back at work
for two years.
Her skills aren't quite up to par.
We're transferring you there
to help her out.
Didn't Mei go to college back in the day?
I remember
she graduated from Dongdu University
of Political Science and Law.
What's the use?
She's out of practice.
Years ago,
she got dragged down
by her husband's political issues
and was sent down to do accounting.
She barely spent any time as a judge.
Back then,
the division sent Sun over.
But this guy is too blunt.
And Mei Fang is quite sensitive.
The two of them often...
Got it.
But, Chief Judge,
I'm even blunter than Sun.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Ate too fast at lunch.
Feeling a bit queasy.
Xia.
The division is in a tough spot now.
We don't feel comfortable
giving her big cases.
But if we always give her small cases,
she's not satisfied.
She has repeatedly
approached the leadership,
asking if the division
doesn't trust her.
What do you think we should do?
Well,
what do you want me to say?
Just say that you'll definitely
help Mei Fang professionally,
and that you'll mind your methods—
protecting Mei Fang's self-esteem
while making sure the work is solid.
Say, ''Chief Judge, don't worry.
Leave it to me.''
Is that okay?
Such a trivial case.
Dragged from the first instance
all the way to appeal.
Assault, minor injuries,
and they give him three years—
the maximum sentence.
Yet the family is still making a fuss.
Xia.
Threatening suicide, filing petitions...
If you ask me,
we should just ignore them.
I'm done. Take your time.
Okay.
Yu,
I was just looking for you.
There is a letter for you
at the gatehouse.
He said it's been there
for over a month,
and you didn't go get it.
He asked me to bring it to you.
[Recipient: Yu Gaoyuan
Sender: Zhang Lihui]
You owe me a meal later.
Thanks.
This name is a girl.
Not bad, Yu.
High standards, huh?
From the Supreme People's Procuratorate,
and you can't even be bothered?
Does it have anything to do with you?
Just kidding.
She was my classmate.
You're back.
Yes.
Mentor.
Look at these.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Careful, it is so hot.
Have a seat.
You're so clumsy.
What's wrong?
Look at these hearings we've held.
Dozens of defendants
all mentioned someone
named Xiaoguang.
He must be
the ringleader of this hooligan gang.
But look at this indictment.
His name wasn't
mentioned at all.
So what are you suggesting?
It's not about what I'm suggesting.
We have to root him out.
For this case,
we only try
what the procuratorate submits.
Why?
No, Mentor.
Such an important
hooligan gang crime,
with dozens of female victims,
including minors
and even suicides—
no matter how we rule, we can't...
No.
I'm worried that when they investigate
for accountability,
it will fall on us.
Look at what's written here.
Xiaoguang instigated it all.
We were just following orders.
Whatever he told us to do,
we did.
Excuse me.
That's what they all said.
Song Xiaoguang.
This is Xiaoguang you mentioned.
Manic psychosis?
Let me tell you.
Why didn't the procuratorate
mention it in the indictment?
Because they can't.
You think you're the only one who noticed?
You think everyone else is blind?
This evaluation report
came with the case file
when it was transferred.
Then this evaluation report
must have issues.
He's currently
staying in a psychiatric hospital,
in a private ward.
That's already
doing the procuratorate a favor.
Wait, who is this guy?
You know the "Song"
in Song Xiaoguang?
It's the Song family.
Silly boy.
Song Xiaoguang,
right?
How do you know?
Who doesn't know?
Everybody in Binjiang knows.
Except you.
What do you mean?
That's Deputy Secretary Song's son.
The infamous crown prince of Binjiang.
You...
Wasting my time,
right?
Absolutely.
Mr. Song started his career in Binjiang.
More than half of the city's officials
are his former subordinates.
If you want to prosecute his only son,
you'd better weigh the consequences first.
Hello, who's this?
It's Chen Yizhong.
Yizhong. What's up?
Are you free tonight?
Let's have dinner together.
What's the catch for this sudden treat?
Is there something urgent?
No, nothing urgent.
Well,
Lu Zeming is here.
Okay, I'll go. Let's bleed him dry.
Okay.
Also,
Yu might come too.
Whatever.
You are here so early.
Great Prosecutor Chen.
Great Judge.
You're even reading at dinner?
Of course.
How long has it been since we last met?
The last time was
in spring,
the tug-of-war.
Right.
Yu led those beefy guys
from your court
and almost pulled me away.
That's because you have no principles.
You switch sides
as soon as someone wins you over.
Who switched sides?
When did I ever switch sides?
Are you two really that busy?
Our courts are right next to each other,
but we haven't seen each other all year.
I'm alright. I'm not that busy.
Xia Yingjie's the busy one.
Running down all day long.
Isn't your Intermediate Court mainly
responsible for second instance trials?
Why are you running down?
The criminal division is especially busy.
Our chief judge always says,
''We're not some grassroots court.
We handle only the most serious cases."
So basically, for every case,
we have to interrogate
and investigate personally.
But shouldn't that be the job
of the police
and your procuratorate?
Right.
Ask your chief judge.
Their chief judge is a bit
like that Mentor in Nanyu.
Who? Zhang?
Their chief judge was transferred
from your procuratorate.
He has
an instinctive,
immense,
and infinite passion
for investigating cases.
Occupational hazard.
Yizhong.
The judge still has to
investigate the case.
Do you think that is right?
In our country's current situation,
I think it's necessary.
Because in my ideal world,
a judge's state should be:
barely look at the case files
before going to court,
then in court,
just listen to both sides,
and making a ruling right there.
Didn't he just say it?
At this stage,
it's hard to be so idealistic.
And it's not just
demanding for you personally.
It has high requirements
from both the prosecution and defense.
True.
Very true.
Look.
The same words, but coming from you
versus me...
Waiter!
Hello. Where is...
Thought you'd chicken out
to avoid an expensive bill.
Excuse me, is this
the private room for the chosen ones?
Come on, friends.
Never fight an unprepared battle.
Spend away!
Chen Yizhong, you order.
Order the most expensive one.
Don't save money
for our Dafang Law Firm.
Otherwise it'll just get
squandered by Yuan anyway.
Let's ask someone who knows how to order.
Okay.
Gaoyuan!
Yu Gaoyuan!
Come on.
Long time no see.
You remember me, huh?
Yu Gaoyuan.
Long time no see.
You, great lawyer,
came here
to guide our work?
I'm here to talk business with you.
Are you kidding me?
I'd have to take off my uniform.
Why are you still like that?
Still so touchy.
Sit down.
Just messing with you.
I'm doing
non-litigation work now.
Who would want to be a criminal defender?
All that work and no money.
Tonight,
Yu Gaoyuan,
let's really tie one on tonight,
and have a proper heart-to-heart.
Okay, have a proper heart-to-heart.
But I quit drinking.
Why did you quit?
Why didn't you quit earlier?
Sir, take a look at this.
Four catties and seven taels,
is this okay?
How much?
Who is so thoughtful?
Me.
Xia.
Serve it.
Hurry up.
Take your seat.
Sure.
What's your name, sweetheart?
Xiaohong.
Right, Xiaohong.
I'm not dancing.
Come on, let's dance.
Come on.
Shake it.
I thought you loved drinking?
You don't wanna drink? Drink up!
Come on,
let's shake it.
Shake it.
All right.
Sure.
Shake it.
I'm tired. I'm going back first.
Aren't you leaving with them?
I'm off.
Stop dancing. Let's go back.
Let's dance a little longer.
Now you don't want to drink?
You don't wanna have a few drinks
and do something reckless again?
What?
I saw Zhang Lihui a few days ago
at Mr. Zhou's house.
How is she?
Did you know
she's become kinda withdrawn
and closed off?
What do you mean?
Ask yourself.
Ask myself what?
We lost contact after graduation.
What happened between me and Zhang Lihui
is none of your business.
Yu Gaoyuan,
can you talk like a normal person?
Mr. Lu.
What do you want me to say?
What do you want to hear?
I want to slap you.
Can you beat me?
Let's try.
Try it.
Can I beat you?
It's fine.
You drank too much.
Hit me.
Hit me!
All right.
You've had too much?
I'll tell you one last time:
What's between me and Zhang Lihui
is none of your business.
You're drunk. Let's drop it.
Go sit down.
Now that you've made money,
eaten lobster,
and put on a suit,
you're acting all high and mighty
in front of old classmates.
You're drunk. Enough.
Go back and sit down.
Let's go.
Go sit down.
Chen Yizhong,
I'm telling you right here and now:
I'm officially falling out
with Yu Gaoyuan.
Not that we were ever close anyway.
You're really like this, huh.
Where is Xia Yingjie?
She left.
None of you
think highly of me.
You brought this on yourself.
Who can you blame?
I drank too much,
lost control,
and kissed her. So what?
Now the rest of my life
is about paying for that.
I'm not doing anything else.
She wrote letters to me.
I never replied to a single one.
Doesn't that show my stance?
I don't want to affect
or interfere with her life.
What do I need to do now
to satisfy you all?
You made a mistake,
yet you ignore her.
And you're arguing with me here.
Shouldn't you give her an explanation?
Have you said a single word
to her to this day?
All she wants is an explanation.
Ignoring her isn't a stance.
It's running away.
Same thing with Xia Yingjie.
You two are in the same workplace,
and you can't even
exchange a word.
Why?
I...
Does she ever even look at me properly?
Xia Yingjie and I...
She's unhappy right now.
She needs company and is lonely.
Why don't you go?
Don't run away.
Yingjie,
I hope this letter finds you well.
Did you get the package
I sent you?
There's nothing special inside.
Just salted duck eggs, dried meat,
and salted fish
from our hometown.
They are all things you liked to eat
when you were a child.
I don't know if you
still like them now.
Time flies.
It feels like yesterday
you were still a naive little girl.
And now,
you've been working in Binjiang
for so many years.
I'm so proud of you, my daughter.
I'm genuinely happy for everything
you've achieved.
But still,
I can't help but worry
about you.
Living alone out there,
in life
and at work,
I'm sure you've faced plenty of hardships.
My sweet daughter.
Morning.
I miss you.
Mei.
The chief judge told me to report to you
as your assistant judge.
Come in.
I don't have much experience.
Please correct me if I make mistakes
without holding back.
The chief judge is really
looking out for me.
Knowing my professional skills
aren't up to par,
he sent a talented student
to tutor me.
Please don't say that.
Whether it's life experience
or professional qualifications,
I'm way behind you.
Can I sit here?
Go ahead.
It's all thanks to you
that I get to enjoy
this two-person office.
What about Sun?
Was he transferred to your department?
Yes.
That's good.
He's outgoing and likes to chat.
It's a great fit for him to be over there.
He said he misses being here.
What's there to miss?
There are no big cases here,
just trivial matters all day.
When you get old,
even dogs despise you,
and the leaders don't care about you.
Now that you're with me,
you'll have to put up with a lot.
Don't say that.
In our criminal division,
every case matters.
If it's not a life sentence
or the death penalty,
it wouldn't be sent
to the Intermediate Court.
Right?
How dare you hit me!
Let go of my mom!
Let me go! Let me go!
You stole our business.
Mom, stop fighting! Let's go home!
Stop fighting!
Mom!
You are a bourgeois capitalist roader,
wearing this thing around your neck.
Mom! Mom!
You're a capitalist roader.
Pick it up and put it on!
Let go of my mom!
Let me go!
Yizhong!
Shut up!
See? Aren't they beasts?
What do you think of the evidence?
The evidence is conclusive.
These people, even now,
still don't think
they've committed a crime
and spout self-righteous nonsense.
The confessions match up.
And there are many witnesses at the scene.
Over a hundred bystanders
watched it happen,
and the victim's injury report
is already out.
Tian Shuzhen isn't just physically hurt—
she's also suffered severe
psychological trauma.
Then there's no problem.
Just prosecute them.
Yes.
I'm going to the scene
to investigate again.
Make sure the case file is bulletproof.
Your case file
is already very solid.
Is that necessary?
I want to ask those people
what they were thinking.
Chen, I've told you before.
A case to a prosecutor
is like a patient to a surgeon.
Once all the indicators
for surgery are met,
you perform the operation.
You don't ask the patient
what they're thinking.
Otherwise, you really can't do this job.
Mentor, I feel...
I feel this is wrong.
If we prosecutors
don't pour our emotions
into our own work,
wouldn't we just become tools?
Prosecutors are the symbol of
the pursuit of fairness and justice.
How does this fairness
and justice come about?
It comes from us
handling cases
one by one.
Alright then.
Just go ahead.
But don't get too invested.
Why am I telling you this?
Because
there was a female comrade
in our office before.
She kept getting assigned
these brutally horrific cases.
She was so committed.
And after all those cases
were closed,
she had a mental breakdown.
She's still on medical leave.
That won't happen to me.
Don't worry.
My mind's not gonna break.
I have to see what's wrong
with these people's minds.
Okay, that's good.
That Tian Shuzhen is pretty,
and she attracts men.
The business across the street
was all taken by her.
No, Director Du.
You can't say that.
Everyone around here knows
that Wang's family got pushed out by them,
that they couldn't even make ends meet.
With an eight-year-old kid at home,
but to live on air?
His wife, Liang Yuemin,
is very capable.
Carried the whole family
on her shoulders.
Good woman,
warm-hearted.
But she's got a temper.
And her husband Wang Youxi
is spineless.
Plus, I heard...
I heard he's impotent.
That's why
he's afraid of his wife.
Director Du.
You're here.
-Director.
-You're here.
Perfect timing.
These are comrades from the Procuratorate.
They are here for the matter
between Wang's and Sun's families.
Hurry up and tell them
what you saw that day.
I've said it 800 times.
What else is there to say?
Just tell them
what you saw that day.
All that pale skin.
You were all there that day, right?
Yes, of course we were.
It would be a loss
to miss such a big drama.
We've been talking about this
over meals for days.
I heard your wife even
fought with you over this.
Well, I mean,
everyone's been saying
that Sun Rong's wife is a looker.
Indeed.
She has a really good figure.
I meant it as a compliment.
A-And she got mad.
True.
She's much better than your wife.
Why you gotta bring my wife into it?
What's my wife got to do with this?
Stop fighting.
What're you getting worked up for?
Stop.
What?
Chen,
don't stoop to their level.
Let me apologize
on their behalf, okay?
Why are you apologizing for them?
I actually grew up
on this street.
These people are indeed rogues,
but I can understand them.
They are poorly educated
and have no other joy in life.
A neighbor's troubles
is half a year's gossip.
Besides, this time
a woman was stripped in public.
I'm telling you, don't make excuses.
When this happened,
not a single person on the street
stepped in to stop it.
So what if they are poorly educated?
Is that an excuse?
I'm telling you,
everyone who was watching that day
is an accomplice.
But we can't prosecute
all those hundreds of people, can we?
So it all has to be pinned on them!
Chen, calm down.
Sorry, it has nothing to do with you.
Let's grab some noodles before going back.
The cafeteria is closed anyway.
I'm not eating.
What? Why?
I won't eat anything from this street.
Song Xiaoguang.
Yes.
In his current condition,
he's not available for visitors.
He doesn't need to see me.
I just want to take a look.
Then what is the purpose
of you taking a look?
Taking a look is the purpose itself.
Xiaowen.
How is Song Xiaoguang doing today?
He just finished his treatment
and was injected with midazolam.
He's resting now.
Look.
It's
unfortunate.
Why don't you come back another day?
Director Zhao, here's the thing:
I'd like to ask—
your prescription forms,
treatment records,
and medication records
are all kept on file, right?
Of course.
We're responsible to our patients.
Understood.
Make sure they're preserved well.
They might come in handy later.
If there is any inaccuracy or fabrication,
the relevant personnel
will be prosecuted for forging evidence.
If convicted,
they'll face legal consequences.
At that time,
it's very likely
our court will reopen
a new medical appraisal.
I've said too much.
You go ahead.
Let's go.
Comrade.
How about this?
Please follow me.
Sorry for the trouble, Director Zhao.
Thank you.
Come in.
It's quite narrow.
It's fine.
We're here.
This way.
Mom.
Here, have a bite.
This is how she is now.
It's so hot,
but she wraps herself up tightly
with clothes every day.
Look,
she is still covered
with such a thick quilt.
She doesn't eat or drink.
I'm worried that if this goes on,
she won't live long.
How about sending her to the hospital?
We did.
She couldn't stay there.
She made a fuss in the hospital.
She spat at strangers
and howled.
The doctors couldn't do anything.
Besides,
we really have no money left.
Get her treated first.
You can claim it all back.
Claim from him?
What can he compensate with?
If his family had money,
would they fight with us for business
and cause all this mess?
He has to compensate no matter what.
I'm putting my words here.
Even if he has to sell everything he owns,
he must compensate you.
She is ruined.
Even if he compensates,
can he compensate me
with a healthy person?
That day,
if my son hadn't
held me back with all his might
and snatched my knife,
I would really have chopped up
Wang Youxi and his wife.
I'll do it.
Mom.
Move aside.
Mom, it's okay.
Mom.
Don't be afraid.
It's okay.
It's me.
I'm here.
-Mom.
-I'm here. I'm here.
Go get
the rope!
It's okay. Don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid. I'm here.
Write this down.
Sofa.
Fruit knife.
Cigarettes.
Yu.
Yu, Yu.
You can't tell anything from this at all.
That's exactly why
we need to reopen the appraisal procedure.
Comrade Prosecutor,
I am really a good person.
I haven't done anything bad,
And in business,
I never cheat on measurements.
Ask anyone around here
if you don't believe me.
Never done anything wrong?
On the street,
in front of so many people,
you molested a woman.
What else do you want to do?
She pushed me to it!
All I did was rip off her clothes.
What did she do to my family,
did you ask?
I was coming back from grocery shopping,
and I saw my wife
and my sister
fighting with Tian Shuzhen.
Then what did you do?
What did you do?
Excuse me.
Move.
What are you doing?
What did you do?
Are you trying to kill her?
Why are you taking her side?
Are you crazy?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Who's talking nonsense?
Go.
Strip her naked.
Do it!
You shouldn't bully people!
I just thought
it was only stripping her clothes off.
I really didn't know.
Our business was booming
before their family
opened a restaurant.
Yuemin.
Youxi.
Here.
I bought you some
loquats and pastries.
They're very sweet.
Take them.
Hope you'll look out for us.
Here, take them.
They're delicious.
Listen to me.
There are only so many people
on our street.
If we open two restaurants,
don't you think this business
will be hard to run?
Yuemin, don't worry.
We definitely won't steal your business.
Rest assured.
Here, take them.
They're really sweet.
If you like them, I'll buy you more.
Youxi, I'm heading back.
Enjoy.
She swore to me,
over and over again,
that she'd never poach my business.
But what happened?
She stole my customers!
And then,
she got even bolder.
We were delivering meals
to a construction site.
She took that contract too.
Liang Yuemin.
You are also a woman.
You should understand how that feels.
And you still stripped her in public
and humiliated her?
Yes,
that's right.
I am also a woman.
Then how can I
make a living with my own two hands,
but she has to rely on
seducing men?
Tian Shuzhen is now
mentally unstable.
Your family did this to her.
You know that?
She's faking it.
I have an eight-year-old son.
I want...
I beg you to give me another chance.
She pushed me to it.
She forced me.
She brought it on herself.
Didn't you try to talk to them?
Talk to them about what?
Persuade them to show remorse.
Get them to offer
as much compensation as possible,
and try to get the victim's forgiveness.
That would help
when it comes to
sentencing.
Even now, he doesn't think
he committed a crime.
Where is the remorse?
Where is the compensation?
Besides, why should the victim
forgive them?
But you haven't tried,
how do you know?
The victim's son is
twelve or thirteen years old.
Right at his doorstep,
he witnessed his mother
being publicly humiliated
and bullied by neighbors.
How can he forgive?
That kid walks past this spot
every day going to and from school.
How can he ever forget that?
Why should he forgive?
Chen,
we can't make decisions for the victim
to express forgiveness.
Likewise, we cannot
make decisions for the victim
-to refuse forgiveness.
-Yes, that's right.
I know you're right about everything.
But on this matter,
I can't accept it.
Do you know what the cruelest war
in the world is?
The cruelest war
is when people
harm each other just to survive.
Don't you think Liang Yuemin's family
is actually quite pitiful too?
These are all excuses.
And I don't think so.
Aren't these just excuses?
Just because you need to survive,
you can harm others?
What kind of logic is that?
If you think
you have to hurt others to survive,
then let me tell you,
if you commit a crime,
you must be punished.
When I was young,
I said the same things.
When you get older,
you will understand
that what ought to be and what actually is
are two different things.
Mentor, if I...
If one day,
I encounter something like this
and I don't even feel angry anymore,
don't even feel sad,
then I'm done.
So have you decided?
What sentence are you planning
to recommend to the court?
The National People's Congress
has clear provisions
on the Strike-Hard Campaign.
For crimes with severe circumstances,
sentencing can exceed the statutory range.
Look, you've been here
for a long time.
Cases of sentencing above
the statutory range have been rare.
But this provision
hasn't been abolished.
We can still use it.
In this case,
I will definitely do my best
to give them the most severe punishment.
That day,
after dawn,
I was walking this way,
and I saw something over there.
I was wondering about it.
I was wondering who dropped their stuff.
Took a closer look,
and it was a plastic bag.
We found something here.
Excuse me.
Captain Liu.
What's the situation?
Aside from here,
in the woods across the river,
we found another part.
Preliminary assessment
is that it washed up during high water.
Captain Liu!
What's going on?
We found a body in a bag.
Mom.
Mom, take it easy.
Slow down. Don't panic.
It might not be Sanhua.
This is Captain Liu.
Captain,
where is my daughter?
Ma'am, please calm down.
We haven't confirmed
that it's your daughter yet.
Please, have a seat.
Right.
Mom, sit down.
How about this?
Tell me first
about your daughter.
My daughter
suddenly stopped contacting us.
I'm so worried.
My eyelids
just keep twitching nonstop.
And I've been having dreams lately.
My daughter came to me in a dream.
She said her husband
killed her
and threw her into the water.
Stop weaving.
It's not worth much.
What's wrong?
Hasn't your foot healed yet?
Comrade.
You are Qian Xingliang, right?
Ten days ago,
specifically on August
11th or 12th,
where were you?
I can't remember.
I don't think
I went anywhere.
Your wife, Yu Sanhua,
came to see you recently, didn't she?
Yes, she did.
I heard
you asked her to come.
Yes.
I had someone pass a message
to talk to her about something.
So,
what did you ask her to come talk about?
Divorce.
She was working in Guangzhou,
and had a lover,
so she wanted to divorce me.
I said fine,
but you have to return
the 2,000 yuan bride price.
Otherwise, no divorce.
Did you talk in this room?
No.
By the river.
I didn't want my mom to hear.
How did it go?
It went badly.
We had a fight.
She said
that unless I got a divorce,
I'd never see her again.
And then?
How did she go back?
She walked along the main road.
She probably
took the bus back.
I didn't see her off.
What time?
I can't remember.
What did you do after that?
I played cards with someone
and didn't go home until dark.